Mandil Malla

Tama-Ku, shukugawara6-6-21lindesidekui103, Kawasaki

+817085570709

mallamandilcoding@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mandil-malla/

_

mandilmalla.000webhostapp.com

As a highly motivated computer engineering graduate with a strong passion for technology, I possess over 6 months of experience in development using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for a company based in Nepal back in 2017. Additionally, I have gained valuable management skills through my experience in my previous work at a restaurant in Japan, where I also achieved Japanese language proficiency test N3 certification. I successfully completed Le Wagon's Web Development Bootcamp this march and have been dedicated to continuously enhancing my skills and staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends.

Experience

JUL 2023 - TILL NOW

System & information management / Workchange Co. Ltd , Tokyo

- Assisting parttime workers on the usage of company application
- Determining different results based on the application
- Thinking of new ideas to implement to existing app

JUN 2019 - JAN 2023

Sub Manager/Antworks Co. Ltd (Restaurant), Tokyo

- Managing the shop
- Managing stocks and shifts
- Guiding newcomers
- Handling kitchen/hall

DEC 2016 - JUN 2017

Programmer/ ABGS Group, Nepal

- Worked on making chat-bots for banks.
- Used php, html, css, js, mysql, git

Education

2011 - 2015

Bachelor in Computer Engineering/Advanced College of Engineering & Management, Nepal

Skills

Html5

Css3/ scss

Ruby / Ruby on Rails

Heroku/ Github pages/Netlify

BootStrap

Javascript

SQL/Mysql

Ms-word/ Ms-Excel

PHP/Laravel

Git

React

Certifications

JAN 2023 - MAR 2023

Web Development/Le Wagon, Tokyo

FEB 2017 - MAY 2017

Front End Development/Halftone Design, Nepal

Personal Projects

Portfolio

- Different projects done through the skills I have learned and learning.
- Over 10+ projects
- Frontend html, css, js, bootstrap, react
- Backend ruby, ruby on rails, php
- www.mandilmalla.me

Languages

- English (Business)
- Japanese(N3)
- Nepali (Native)
- Hindi (conversational)